<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UTS_MOBILE_26780</string>
    <string name="liirklagu">(Lovesick girls) (Lovesick girls) Yeong wonhan bam Changmun eopsneun bange uril gadun love (Love) What can we say? Maebeon apado oechineun love (Love) Dachigo manggajyeodo na Mwol mitgo beotineun geoya Eochapi tteonamyeon sangcheotuseongin chaero miwohage doegreol Kkeutjangeul bogi jeon kkeutnael sun eobseo Iapeumeul gidarin geotcheoreom Ama da jamkkan iljido molla Urin mueol chajaseo hemaeneun geolkka But I don\'t care I\'ll do it over and over Nae sesang sogen neoman isseumyeon dwae We are the lovesick girls Ne meottaero nae salangeul kkeunnael sun eopseo We are the lovesick girls Iapeum eobsin nan amu uimiga eopseo But we were born to be alone Yeah, we were born to be alone Yeah, we were born to be alone But why we still looking for love? No love letters, no X and O\'s No love, never, my exes know No diamond rings, that set in stone To the left, better left alone Didn\'t wanna be a princess, I\'m priceless A prince not even on my list Love is a drug that I quit No doctor could help when I\'m lovesick Ama da jamkkan iljido molla Urin mueol chajaseo hemaeneun geolkka Buranhan nae nunppit soge neol dama Apeudeorado neoman isseumyeon dwae We are the lovesick girls Ne meottaero nae salangeul kkeunnael sun eopseo We are the lovesick girls Iapeum eobsin nan amu uimiga eopseo But we were born to be alone Yeah, we were born to be alone Yeah, we were born to be alone But why we still looking for love Sarangeun slippin\' and fallin\' Sarangeun killin\' your darlin\' Apeuda amulmyeontto chajaoneun i geop eomneun tteollim Deulliji anha what you say Iapeumi nan haengbokae Nareul bulssanghae haneun nega nae nunen deo bulssanghae We are the lovesick girls Ne meottaero nae salangeul kkeunnael sun eopseo We are the lovesick girls Iapeumeobsin nan amu uimiga eopseo One, two (Lovesick girls) Modu gyeolguk tteonagago (Lovesick girls) Nae nunmuri mudyeojyeodo (Lovesick girls) Apeugotto apado (Lovesick girls) But we\'re still looking for love</string>
    <string name="liriklagu2">Today I don\'t feel like doing anything I just wanna lay in my bed Don\'t feel like picking up my phone, so leave a message at the tone \'Cause today I swear I\'m not doing anything I\'m gonna kick my feet up, then stare at the fan Turn the TV on, throw my hand in my pants Nobody\'s gon\' tell me I can\'t, no! I\'ll be lounging on the couch, just chilling in my Snuggie Click to MTV, so they can teach me how to dougie \'Cause in my castle I\'m the freaking man Oh Yes! I said it, I said it, I said it \'cause I can Today I don\'t feel like doing anything I just wanna lay in my bed Don\'t feel like picking up my phone, so leave a message at the tone \'Cause today I swear I\'m not doing anything Nothing at all Woo, ooh, woo, ooh, ooh Nothing at all Woo, ooh, woo, ooh, ooh Tomorrow I\'ll wake up, do some P90X Meet a really nice girl, have some really nice sex And she\'s gonna scream out This is great (Oh my god, this is great) Yeah! I might mess around and get my college degree I bet my old man will be so proud of me But sorry pops, you\'ll just have to wait Oh Yes! I said it, I said it, I said it \'cause I can Today I don\'t feel like doing anything I just wanna lay in my bed Don\'t feel like picking up my phone, so leave a message at the tone \'Cause today I swear I\'m not doing anything No, I ain\'t gonna comb my hair \'Cause I ain\'t going anywhere No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, oh I\'ll just strut in my birthday suit And let everything hang loose Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Oh, today I don\'t feel like doing anything I just wanna lay in my bed Don\'t feel like picking up my phone, so leave a message at the tone \'Cause today I swear I\'m not doing anything Nothing at all Woo, ooh, woo, ooh, ooh Nothing at all Woo, ooh, woo, ooh, ooh Nothing at all</string>
</resources>